shipmentlink.com 2009-06-19

# ShipmentLink - Legal Disclaimer - Privacy and Security Statement

  Privacy and Security Statement 

This Privacy and Security Statement ('Statement') is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use and applies to this web site which is owned and operated by Evergreen Line, Evergreen Marine Corp. (Taiwan) Ltd., Italia Marittima S.p.A., Evergreen Marine (UK) Ltd., Evergreen Marine (Hong Kong) Ltd. and Evergreen Marine (Singapore) Pte Ltd. (hereinafter collectively called the "Carriers") under the domain name www.shipmentlink.com ('ShipmentLink Web site'). You acknowledge and accept that your use of or access to the ShipmentLink Web site indicate your acceptance to this Statement and Terms of Use.  
The followings are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to ShipmentLink Web site:

|   1. | Information Collection  
---|---  
  | The information registered via our website is not made publicly available. We will collect information or data from you in order to send information and promotional material to registered users or new applications to be launched on our website and establish your identity, to tailor our service for your needs and to assist Carriers in providing better services to you. Some of this information may be a form or format that identifies you or another person ('personally identifiable information'). To use some of the services provided by Carriers , you may need to complete various online form(s) where you will be required to provide us with personally identifiable information, such as name and e-mail address.  
  
  2. | Cookies  
---|---  
  | We use "cookies" as a fundamental part of our interaction with your internet browser. A cookie may be set on your computer when you register or "Log In" of our service. So that it can be retrieved by our webpage servers next time and used to determine the extent of repeat usage by a registered user. You are always free to decline Carriers' cookies if your browser permits, though you are limited to using non-registered service of the Carriers' Website.  
  
  3. | Use of Information  
---|---  
  | Personally identifiable information collected from you will generally be used by us in ways set out in this Statement. Carriers use personally identifiable information for marketing purposes, e.g. (i) to remind us to access your account for a better and more personalized service; (ii) to estimate our audience size and to statistically analyze the usage; (iii) to measure and analyze the usage; (iv) to deliver information to you that is targeted to your interests; and (v) to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and improve our service.   
  
  4. | Sharing and Disclosure  
---|---  
  | Without your consent, we will not share your personally identifiable information with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide documents/services you have requested or under the following circumstances:  
  | (i) | We provide the information to agents who work on behalf of Carrier(s) under confidentiality agreements.  
  | (ii) | We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
  | (iii) | We believes that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to violations of Terms of Use.  
  | (iv) | Carriers are authorized, required or permitted by law to disclose the information. Without prejudice to the generality of the immediately preceding paragraph, you hereby consent that Carriers are authorized to disclose personally identifiable information to the following entities, organizations and persons:  
  |   | (i) | Carriers' affiliates;  
  |   | (ii) | our outsourced hosting service providers who manage the services we provide to you;  
  |   | (iii) | your representatives (e.g. your authorized representatives or legal advisers); and  
  |   | (iv) | our professional advisers, including our accountants, auditors and lawyers.  
  
  5. | 0ther Websites Links  
---|---  
  | The Carriers' Web site links to the websites of third party who may collect personally identifiable information about you. In this case, information generated by cookies and information that you provide about yourself may be shared between that third party, the person hosting the third party web sites, Carriers and/or the related parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such third party web sites.  
  
  6. | Third Party Hosting Service  
---|---  
  | We contract with one or more third parties to maintain and host the Carriers' Web site. Therefore, any information you submit, including personally identifiable information, will be placed and stored on a computer server maintained by such third party. Your use of the Carriers' Web site and any provision of information, content or data to the Carriers' Web site constitutes your acknowledgement that such information, content or data could pass through and may be stored in servers outside the control of Carriers and may be accessed by the administrator of such site and others that gain access to Carriers' server or stored files. You agree that Carriers have no liability or responsibility for any disclosure, authorized or unauthorized, resulting from or arising in connection with such pass through or storage of same.  
  
  7. | Disclaimer  
---|---  
  | Carriers assume no responsibility for your any inconvenience, resulting from any unexpected reasons which cause the abnormal operation to web-site. While Carriers are adopting an industry standard technology to protect your personal information, Carriers shall not be liable for the disclosure of your personal information on account of your improper use, or any type of malicious destruction by any third party from the site.  
  
  8. | Internet Security  
---|---  
  | Carriers take reasonable steps to preserve the security of cookies and will use standard industry efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information.  
  
  9. | Edit/Opt-out Registered User's Profile  
---|---  
  | You can review and change the information you submitted and you have the right to request Carriers not to use or retain your personally identifiable information. However, we may retain some of them in our files in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes and, due to technical constraints, such information is never completely removed from our databases.  
  
10. | Important Advice  
---|---  
  | In order to protect your privacy and our proprietary databases and systems, we recommend that you not share any of your personally identifiable information, such as password, or personal identification number, with any third party that would allow them access to sensitive account information. Carriers will never ask you for your password and will not be held responsible for events arising from third parties gaining unauthorized access to your personal information. If the security of your password has been compromised for any reason, you should change your password immediately and notify us for assistance. We also remind you that you may be legally responsible for the processing of data. For example, if you illicitly upload or download and that everything may be traced back to you even if you use a pseudonym.  
  
11. | Changes to this Statement  
---|---  
  | We reserve the right to change these guidelines and disclaimers at any time, and may update this Statement by publishing the revised Statement on the Carriers' Web site.  
  
12. | Questions and Suggestions  
---|---  
  | Please contact us if you have any questions and suggestions regarding this Statement.
